memory-of.com 2007-06-26

# "Memory-of" Privacy Policy

|  |  | Privacy Policy |   
---|---  
  
This privacy policy sets out the type of personal information that we - the Library of Life Foundation Limited and the Library of Life Trust - collect, what we use it for and the rights that you have in relation to this information. By using this website, you accept the terms of this privacy policy.

  1. **Collection of Personal Information**

We shall collect personal information from you in a number of circumstances, including when you register your personal details, when you use our services, or when you enter any promotions over the Library of Life websites, including www.libraryoflife.org, www.libraryoflife.net, www.memory-of.com and www.celebration-of.com. For example, when you register your personal details to create a website, we ask for your name and email address as a minimum requirement. If you choose to purchase any service we will also ask for your credit or bank card details. Once you register and sign into our website, you are not anonymous to us.

  2. **Use of Personal Information**
    1. We will never sell, exchange or divulge your personal information (including your e-mail address) to any third party without your consent, unless we believe that the release of this information is appropriate in order to comply with the law, or to enforce our Terms of Use, or to protect our rights, property or safety, our customers, or other third parties. However, when you purchase services through the website and enter payment information, this information may be transferred to the processing company for transaction authorization and authentication purposes.
    2. We will use your personal information for the purpose of providing the services offered over the Library of Life websites. We may collect information about your historical activity with us and your use of the website. For example, we may record information on our servers from your browser, including your IP address, cookie information, and the pages you visit.
    3. We may send you information about services and features available on our websites or advice on how to use the various tools the site has to offer. We may also send you a newsletter providing this information and services offered by our partners.
  3. **Updating Personal Information**

It is your responsibility to ensure that we have your correct contact information. This will enable us to provide you with the best service and website possible.

  4. **Removal of Personal Information**

If would like us to remove all the personal information we have about you from our records please contact us via the details provided on the Contact Us page. Please note that we require certain key information from you in order to provide you with our services, and if you ask us to remove all or part such information you may no longer be able to use or access the website or parts of it.

  5. **Minors**

The consent of a parent, guardian or educational supervisor shall be required before any child under the age of 16 can register their personal details. The parent, guardian or educational supervisor will accept full responsibility for our use of this information, in accordance with this policy.

  6. **Security**

We will take reasonable precautions to ensure that all the personal information that you have submitted via the website remains confidential. As required by the Data Protection Act 1998 we have strict security procedures regarding the storage and disclosure of personal information.

  7. **Transfer of Data**

In order to provide you with certain services and/or products we may need to transfer your personal information outside the European Economic Area, including to the USA, where data protection laws are not comparable to those within the EEA. By submitting your personal information to us you consent to such a transfer.

  8. **Terms of Use, Privacy Policy and Revisions**

This policy forms part of our Terms of Use which governs your use of this website, (both of which may be changed or updated from time to time without notice). By using this website you are deemed to accept the Terms of Use and the terms and conditions of this policy. Our use of your personal information is subject to the terms and conditions of our policy in force at the time when we use the information in question.

Last Updated on July 24th 2005.
